Come on, we're shining, running, forever!
The sea is calling out, so ride the waves!
We're all together as one,
so let's sail in the sun!
All our dreams are never-ending, so
let's wake up, wake up, wake up, wake up!
Heartbeat, we will be one! Go ahead!
Even though our hearts have
traveled different paths.
We are best friends.
Our freedom is our only compass.
That's pointing us along the
many roads that come together.
We will keep on running forward every day.
Go east, go west.
As long as we keep looking to the horizon.
We'll see everything all crystal clear.
We're all so thrilled that we
can't wait until the dawn arrives.
So we'll just bring the
sun ourselves to know.
If the winds blow, is waiting
where we should be going, go?
That's right, we're
shining, running forever!
All of our dreams will
merge into one piece.
No matter where we go,
we'll be fine and free.
Cause all our treasure is our strength.
Come on, we're shining, running forever!
The sea is coming out, so ride away!
We're all together as well, so
let's just stay with us, son!
All our dreams are never-ending, so
let's wake up, wake up, wake up, wake up!
Heartbeat, we will be one, go ahead!
My darkness will swallow the
world, just you wait and see!
You think I'll lose to you?
I'm gonna be king of the pirates!
Roger's treasure belongs to me!
We'll ride non-stop and travel farther
than we've ever gone And then tomorrow we
will find suspense And then commence to
live out another day so intense
That's right, we're shining,
running forever Let's go along
with curiosity Our feelings lead
the way straight to a brand new day Into
another adventure Come on, we're shining,
running forever Open the map inside your
heart and see No matter where we end up,
our mods will never give up There's a fire
in our dreams And you can never, never,
never, never stop it We
will be one, go ahead!
My face is so sexy!
I don't know much about art, but scams
are not supposed to look like this!
This is so tacky!
What did you do to us?
Don't interrupt me!
Unless you want to compliment my figure.
They won't get away from me that easily.
There's one kind of artist I can't stand.
It's an escape artist.
Get back here or I'll make you
into stiff figures this time.
We don't have to listen to you.
It's not like you can do anything
to us if you can't even reach us.
If she keeps using that
weird power of hers,
the Sunny could end up
as a finger painting.
or something else ugly and useless.
I'm sure Franky will
be furious either way.
Do you think that we can fix it?
For now, the best we can do is try to
stop her from screwing it up even more.
That's why we have to keep our
attention out here, away from the sunny.
Come on.
All right, it's time to bring it up.
Well, don't just sit there, you buffoons.
Do something before they get away.
I don't care how you do it.
Just bring me Momonosuke.
Yes, right away, ma 'am.
My soul is being bombarded by such
marvelous artistic teachers today.
I want to create.
Oh no, she's doing it again.
Ah, excuse me.
We're over here.
Yeah, aim this way.
Forget about the ship.
We're the ones you want, aren't we?
I can see it.
Another vision of freedom and beauty.
Now, let's all express
ourselves, shall we?
It's too late!
She'll ruin the sun for sure!
We're in big trouble!
Sonny, it's all messed up now.
Oh, my, oh, my.
Nice try, uncultured swine.
The young master has instructed me to
kidnap Momonosuke and commandeer your ship.
And without your vessel,
you Straw Hats will have to be very creative
to find another way out of Dressrosa.
Our plan didn't work!
I don't need medical attention.
Get out of my way!
You need treatment.
Our job is to manage the injuries of
all the competitors, especially guests.
Treatment?
Let people kill each
other for an audience.
What do you care if I get hurt?
Whoa!
Your head's bleeding.
Take your helmet off so I can take a look.
Don't touch my helmet.
Are you all right, sir?
That looks painful.
I told you I don't need your help.
Let them treat you.
Your injuries are too serious.
Here.
Move.
I can't walk on my own. Yes, sir.
Take the stairs down to the basement.
Rebecca, I'm sorry.
Straw Hat is competing
as we speak, Diamante.
After the match is fine, then.
So Joker is ordering me
to murder Straw Hat now?
Dolphy's a generous leader.
Even though you lost the tournament,
he's giving you one more
chance to redeem yourself.
You should be happy your task is so easy.
Make sure he's taken care of
before the competition ends.
You can do it!
Keep pegging in there!
You do want to become an executive
of the family, don't you?
So, Cavendish, I heard you was
trying to off that Lucy guy.
Bartolomeo, was it?
Well done making it this far, but my
business with Lucy doesn't concern you.
That's where you're wrong, pretty boy.
Lucy ain't yours to kill.
Oh, I see.
You want to.
He is hogging the limelight,
but no one else can touch him.
Ooh, scary.
Let's just say he and I have a connection.
The contestants are dropping like flies!
The Battle of Bloxie
is getting interesting!
It would appear to be anybody's
game now, ladies and gentlemen.
You may notice that we have one competitor
who literally stands out from the crowd!
Blox!
This warrior is part of a new generation
from Elbath, the giant country.
Give it up for Pirudin!
He's huge!
How is this a fair match-up?
If you think I'm unstoppable now.
just wait till i get my hands on that
flame flame fruit with that power i can be
king of the giants one punch and it's over
just like clockwork at
this rate no one will
be able to meet this
guy well actually maybe
i should take that back we got our out of
control ball running
loose in the arena unfazed
by these tough contenders this wild beast
wants killed Twenty-one
death row prisoners
during the previous battle
in this very Corsia.
A Grim Reaper through and through,
let's hear it for our favorite
rampaging beast, Ruta Ball!
Yet despite his savagery, one of our
contestants seems to have befriended him.
He's a mysterious newcomer,
but his strength and talent makes
him an instant crowd favorite, Lucy!
Woo-hoo!
Yeah!
Go, Lucy!
Look at that guy go!
I'm rooting for him!
I told you, you have to be impartial.
Yeah, that's a good boy!
Run him over!
People love him without
even knowing who he is!
He's something else?
Faster! Faster!
Wait, are you really gonna fight that guy?
You made a big mistake.
Crap! Lucy, run! Go!
No!
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
The ball!
Aunt Lucy!
This is a tragedy, folks!
Talk about a mismatch!
The rookie from Elbam is victorious!
Both of them in one swing!
That's such a terrible way to go!
Sir, look over there!
I can't bear to!
Lucy just fell the giant!
That was incredible, Lucy!
My heart's beating out of my chest!
With fighters like this, can you blame me?
A single contender is turning
this competition on its head!
Just when you think it's
over, Lucy has done it again!
Don't worry, Lucy. Let's go.
Just who is this mysterious
Luffy, and where did he come from?
Yeah, a real mystery.
Unbelievable.
I never imagined he was this strong.
What do you think you're doing, giant?
You're still inside the ring.
Want to take a nap?
Then do it someplace else.
Hyrule and Ghost flying!
Is some kind of explosion to blame?
What just happened?
Tell me!
Hang on, that wasn't an explosion!
Let's not forget, even without
Hirudan, Bloxie's loaded with power!
That powder keg punch was generated by a
man with some distinctly shaped shoulders!
Edeo!
The one who rocked the giant right
out of the ring was none other than
the two-time champion of the new
World Central Fighting Tournament,
Destruction Cannon Edeo!
But wait, that's not the only
fight you want to keep an eye on.
Trio of gangsters hailing from
the Kano Kingdom in the Far East,
each with a truly unique fighting style.
It's useless.
That's their patented Isokan
fighting style, a .k .a.
the Eight-Impact Fist.
It powers straight through
shields and armor alike.
We are witnessing the might of the Habusui
army, forged from centuries of history.
Their technique is truly one of a kind.
If we can take you down, Qin Zhao,
it's almost as big a prize
as winning the competition.
Ready, boys?
Don't get ahead of yourselves.
You brats haven't earned
the right to challenge me!
The Conqueror's honking.
No surprise there.
He was a legendary
pirate worth 500 million.
There's only one man I want to fight.
Don't get in my way!
I gotta thank you, Qin Zhao.
You're giving me plenty to work with.
Hm?
What's this?
Looks like not everyone's
susceptible to Qin Zhao's Haki!
And now he's collecting spare weapons!
This is truly the dark horse of
the competition, Shaun the Bandit!
A bounty hunter whose
reputation has earned him
the wrath of every major
pilot across the new world!
Not so fast!
Huh?
You and I have a score we need to settle!
Think I'd forget you, the man responsible
for getting my partner locked away?
The weapons I retrieve are my
bullets, and I am the sniper!
If that partner of yours was so important,
why didn't you prove it by
breaking him out of prison?
Like that idiot who did
a couple of years back?
What the the guy's already out
cold—why is kelly still wailing on him!
him
Take a breather, big bro.
That guy ain't even conscious
anymore. That's plenty.
You know, in hindsight, I should have you.
Did you hear what he said?
That bastard called me shorty. Hey, Bobby.
Do I look short to you? Huh?
Not one bit, no.
I mean if anything you're a giant of
a man you hear what he said dickhead
That's enough.
He's learned his lesson
I helped back the wrong guy again
Try to say that again,
and I'll jab both your eyes out then Bobby
don't you even think of slowing me down?
Just pace yourself.
It's a long fight That's the ultra
violent style of the Funk Brothers.
There's not a soul in
the criminal underworld
that doesn't know the
names of these siblings.
And based off what I'm reading, they're
powerful enough to take down pirates!
worth over a hundred million.
Bunch of squawking colors from over there.
Leave it if it takes all day!
They look like nothing but a couple
of two-bit street fighters to me.
I guess we'll find out.
How about you show me what you're made of?
I'm talking to you, shrimp.
Brother, no!
Geez, pal.
So weak!
Or perhaps the hub of sweet
armies just overpowered!
But still, how disappointing!
Hey, do you hear me?
You let everyone down!
You can't pick sides!
So, you ready little brother?
Cause you're next! Wait a sec!
I don't even know how to fight!
I've never done this for real!
Not in my entire life!
You will now!
He turned his back and cowered!
These brothers are pathetic!
That broke my accent too.
It doesn't make sense.
That blade was infused with armament Haki.
His body is ridiculously strong.
You okay, bro?
That...
that bastard had the
nerve to call me a shrimp.
Hurry up, Bobby.
Put it on for me.
Fine.
There's no way!
I can't believe what I'm
seeing right now! Boo!
Boo from the Cardo Kingdom
is taking a hell of a beating!
He is down for the count!
But who's not punching him?
The cowardly younger brother Bobby?
Or could it be the weakling
older brother Kelly?
Why, it appears to be Kelly!
Surprising, given his
sudden change in appearance!
Who you calling a shrimp?
Let that be a lesson!
Next time, wise guy,
I'll rip your throat out!
Wow!
During this mayhem, it appears
Lucy's helmet got knocked off!
Hey, give that back to me!
You know, I heard a very
peculiar tale, Lucy.
A rumor about a pirate with a 400 million
bounty by the name of Straw Hat Luffy.
who secretly entered this competition.
Straw Hat!
Don Chin Chow is cutting his way across
the arena, but who's he got his sights on?
I sure hope you're watching this, Garp,
because I'm about to kill your grandson.
And we are down to the last 40 contenders
remaining in Block C's Battle Royale.
The field has been weeded down
to only the strongest fighters.
It's anyone's game, but who will win?